Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Mail Log Files, 1991-1995; I.
  - Office of the Provost, 8.
    - Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 8.14.4.
      - 8.14.4. Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - 8.14.4. Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - 8.14.4. Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Rhodes Scholars, 8.14.5.
      - 801.14E. Rhodes Scholars, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - 8.14.5. Rhodes Scholars, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - University Center for Instructional Resources (UCIR), 8.15.
      - 809.00. University Center for Instructional Resources (UCIR), 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - 8.15. University Center for Instructional Resources (UCIR), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - University Libraries, 8.16.
      - 804.00. University Libraries, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - 8.16. University Libraries, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - 8.16. University Libraries, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - 8.16. University Libraries, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Task Force on Intellectual Property Rights, 8.16.1.
      - 8.16.1. Task Force on Intellectual Property Rights, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
    - Center for Philosophy of Science, 8.17.
      - 801.10. Center for Philosophy of Science, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - 8.17. Center for Philosophy of Science, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - 8.17. Center for Philosophy of Science, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - 8.17. Center for Philosophy of Science, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Development, 8.18.
      - 805.02. Faculty Development, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - 8.18. Faculty Development, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - 8.18. Faculty Development, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - 8.18. Faculty Development, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
    - Chancellor's Distinguished Teaching Awards, 8.18.1.
      - 805.02A. President's Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - 8.18.1. Chancellor's Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - 8.18.1. Chancellor's Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - 8.18.1. Chancellor's Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Chancellor's Distinguished Research Awards, 8.18.2.
      - 805.02B. President's Distinguished Research Awards, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - 8.18.2. Chancellor's Distinguished Research Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - 8.18.2. Chancellor's Distinguished Research Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - 8.18.2. Chancellor's Distinguished Research Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Chancellor's Distinguished Public Service Award, 8.18.4.
      - 8.18.4. Chancellor's Distinguished Public Service Award, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - University Press, 8.19.
      - 801.13. University Press, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 23-24)
      - 8.19. University Press, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 25-26)
      - 8.19. University Press, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - 8.19. University Press, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 28-29)
    - University Press Board of Visitors, 8.19.1.
      - 8.19.1. University Press Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Air Force Aerospace Studies, Army Military Science, ROTC, 8.20.
      - 805.01. Air Force Aerospace Studies, Army Military Science, ROTC, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - 8.20. Air Force Aerospace Studies, Army Military Science, ROTC, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - 8.20. Air Force Aerospace Studies, Army Military Science, ROTC, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 8.20. Air Force Aerospace Studies, Army Military Science, ROTC, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Academic Support Services for Student Athletes (ASSSA), 8.21.
      - 8.21. Academic Support Services for Student Athletes (ASSSA), 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - University Community Education Program (UCEP), 8.22.
      - 8.22. University Community Education Program, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 8.22. University Community Education Program, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 8.22. University Community Education Program, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Bradford Campus, 8.23.1.
      - 806.01. Bradford Campus, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - 8.23.1. Bradford Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - 8.23.1. Bradford Campus, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - 8.23.1. Bradford Campus, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Bradford Advisory Board, 8.23.1.1.
      - 8.23.1.1. Bradford Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Greensburg Campus, 8.23.2.
      - 806.02. Greensburg Campus, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - 8.23.2. Greensburg Campus, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Greensburg Advisory Board, 8.23.2.1.
      - 8.23.2.1. Greensburg Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - 8.23.2.1. Greensburg Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - 8.23.2.1. Greensburg Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Johnstown Campus, 8.23.3.
      - 8.23.3. Johnstown Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - 8.23.3. Johnstown Campus, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - 8.23.3. Johnstown Campus, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Johnstown Advisory Board, 8.23.3.1.
      - 8.23.3.1. Johnstown Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - 8.23.3.1. Johnstown Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - 8.23.6. Johnstown Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Titusville Campus, 8.23.4.
      - 806.04. Titusville Campus, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - 8.23.4. Titusville Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - 8.23.4. Titusville Campus, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - 8.23.7. Titusville Campus, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Titusville Advisory Board, 8.23.4.1.
      - 806.04A. Titusville Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - 8.23.8. Titusville Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Associate Provost, Vijai Singh, 807.00.
      - 807.00. Associate Provost, Vijai Singh, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Space Management, 8.24.
      - 8.24. Space Management, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - 8.24. Space Management, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Institute of Politics, 8.25.
      - 801.05B. Institute of Politics, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - 8.25. Institute of Politics, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - 8.25. Institute of Politics, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - 8.25. Institute of Politics, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Urban and Community Services, 8.25.1.
      - 8.25.1. Urban and Community Services, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Provost Search, 8.26.
      - 8.26. Provost Search, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Indemnification Policy, 8.28.
      - 8.28. Indemnification Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 9.
    The 9.0 Mail Log contains everything related to the Health Sciences at the University of Pittsburgh. This includes correspondence with the Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, Thomas Detre, and material from the National Science Foundation. It also includes correspondence and other materials on the schools that report to the Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences: Medicine, Dental Medicine, Health and Rehabilitation Sciences, Nursing, Pharmacy and Public Health. These records also include correspondence and reports from the individual schools' Boards of Visitors. Materials involving relationships with federal and local entities, such as the National Science Foundation, are also present here.
    - Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 9.0.
      - 900.00. Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - 9.0. Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 40-42)
      - 9.0. Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - 9.0. Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
    - Governor's School of Excellence in Health Professions, 9.0.1.
      - 9.0.1. Governor's School of Excellence in Health Professions, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Search Committee for Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 9.0.2.
      - 9.0.2. Search Committee for Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - 9.0.2. Search Committee for Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - 9.0.2. Search Committee for Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Center for Neural Basis of Cognition (CNBC), 9.0.3.
      - 9.0.3. Center for Neural Basis of Cognition, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - National Surgical Adjuvant Breast and Bowel Project (NSABP), 9.0.4.
      - 9.0.4. National Surgical Adjuvant Breast and Bowel Project (NSABP), 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Tissue Engineering Initiative (PTEI), 9.0.5.
      - 9.0.5. Pittsburgh Tissue Engineering Initiative, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - School of Medicine, 9.1.
      - 901.00. School of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - 9.1. School of Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - 9.1. School of Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 15-19)
      - 9.1. School of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - School of Medicine Board of Visitors, 9.1.1.
      - 901.00A. School of Medicine Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - 9.1.1. School of Medicine Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - 9.1.1. School of Medicine Board of Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Dickson Prize Lectures, 9.1.2.
      - 9.1.2. Dickson Prize Lectures, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - 9.1.2. Dickson Prize Lectures, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 9.1.2. Dickson Prize Lectures, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Center for Emergency Medicine, 9.1.3.
      - 9.1.3. Center for Emergency Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Center for Medical Ethics, 9.1.5.
      - 9.1.5. Center for Medical Ethics, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - 9.1.5. Center for Medical Ethics, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Neuroscience Center, 9.1.6.
      - 9.1.6. Neuroscience Center, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 9.1.6. Neuroscience Center, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Transplants, 9.1.7.
      - 901.00G. Transplants, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 9.1.7. Transplants, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 9.1.7. Transplants, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 9.1.7. Transplants, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Heinz Nutrition Center, 9.1.8.
      - 9.1.8. Heinz Nutrition Center, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Orthopaedic Surgery, 9.1.9.
      - 901.00I. Orthopaedic Surgery, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
      - 9.1.9. Orthopaedic Surgery, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - 9.1.9. Orthopaedic Surgery, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 9.1.9. Orthopaedic Surgery, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Sports and Preventative Medicine Institute, 9.1.14.
      - 9.1.14. Sports and Preventative Medicine Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee, Faculty of Medicine, 9.1.15.
      - 9.1.15. Executive Committee, Faculty of Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - 9.1.15. Executive Committee, Faculty of Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - 9.1.15. Executive Committee, Faculty of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - School of Dental Medicine, 9.2.
      - 903.00. School of Dental Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
      - 9.2. School of Dental Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - 9.2. School of Dental Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 25-27)
      - 9.2. School of Dental Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
      - 9.2. School of Dental Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - School of Dental Medicine Board of Visitors, 9.2.1.
      - 9.2.1. School of Dental Medicine Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences (SHRS), 9.3.
      - 9.3. School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences (SHRS), 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - 9.3. School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences (SHRS), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
      - 9.3. School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences (SHRS), 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - SHRS Board of Visitors, 9.3.1.
      - 904.01. SHRS Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - 9.3.1. SHRS Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - 9.3.1. SHRS Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - School of Nursing, 9.4.
      - 9.4. School of Nursing, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - 9.4. School of Nursing, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - 9.4. School of Nursing, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - School of Nursing Board of Visitors, 9.4.1.
      - 9.4.1. School of Nursing Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - 9.4.1. School of Nursing Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - 9.4.1. School of Nursing Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - School of Pharmacy, 9.5.
      - 9.5. School of Pharmacy, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - 9.5. School of Pharmacy, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - 9.5. School of Pharmacy, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - School of Pharmacy Board of Visitors, 9.5.1.
      - 9.5.1. School of Pharmacy Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - 9.5.1. School of Pharmacy Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 9.6.
      - 907.00. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - 9.6. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - 9.6. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - 9.6. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 27-28)
      - 9.6. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - 9.6. Graduate School of Public Health (GSPH), 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - GSPH Board of Visitors, 9.6.1.
      - 9.6.1. GSPH Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Federal and Local Relations, 9.7.
      - 203.00. Commonwealth Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - 204.00. Federal and Local Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - 9.7. Federal and Local Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 8-10)
      - 9.7. Federal and Local Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 11-14)
      - 9.7. Federal and Local Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 15-17)
    - National Science Foundation, 9.7.1.
      - 204.02. National Science Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - 9.7.1. National Science Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - 9.7.1. National Science Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
      - 9.7.1. National Science Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
    - U.S. Department of Health Services, 9.7.2.
      - 204.03. U.S. Department of Health Services, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - 9.7.2. U.S. Department of Health Services, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - 9.7.2. U.S. Department of Health Services, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Department of Education, 9.7.3.
      - 9.7.3. U.S. Department of Education, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - 9.7.3. U.S. Department of Education, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 10-11)
      - 9.7.3. U.S. Department of Education, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Urban Redevelopment Authority, 9.7.4.
      - 9.7.4. Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - 9.7.4. Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 9.7.6.
      - 9.7.6. Chamber of Commerce, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - 9.7.6. Chamber of Commerce, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - 9.7.6. Chamber of Commerce, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
  - University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 10.
    The records in this subseries focus on the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, or UPMC. They include the meeting minutes of the Board of Directors for UPMC and other hospitals. They also include correspondence and information relating to the acquisition by UPMC of various hospitals and centers in the region. In addition, it contains material regarding the University of Pittsburgh Cancer Institute as well as the Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic.
    - University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 10.0.
      - 908.00. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 20-21)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 2-13)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 2-13)
      - 10.0. University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC), 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - University of Pittsburgh Health Care Task Force, 10.1.
      - 908.00A. University of Pittsburgh Health Care Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - 10.1. University of Pittsburgh Health Care Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
      - 10.1. University of Pittsburgh Health Care Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
      - 10.1. University of Pittsburgh Health Care Task Force, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Presbyterian University Hospital, 10.2.
      - 908.01. Presbyterian University Hospital, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 7-10)
      - 908.01. Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic/Presbyterian University Hospital Merger, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - 10.2. Presbyterian University Hospital, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - 10.2. Presbyterian University Hospital, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - 10.2. Presbyterian University Hospital, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Eye and Ear Hospital, 10.4.
      - 10.4. Eye and Ear Hospital, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - 10.4. Eye and Ear Hospital, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC), 10.5.
      - 908.04. Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC), 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - 10.5. Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC), 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - 10.5. Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC), 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - 10.5. Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC), 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Montefiore Hospital, 10.6.
      - 10.6. Montefiore Hospital, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 10.7.
      - 909.00. Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - 10.7. Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - 10.7. Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - 10.7 Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 11.
    The material in the 11 Mail Log contains records of the Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, and the various departments and offices this position oversaw. The material in these files includes information on annual budget requests and appropriations from the state; capital projects planning; information on and correspondence from departments such as Public Safety, Property Management, and Human Resources; and information on the university's Master Space Plan in 11.8.
    - Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 11.0.
      - 700.00. Senior Vice Chancellor for Business and Finance, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - 702.00. Vice President for Finance, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 3-12)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 1-8)
      - 11.0 Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 1995-1996 (Box 44, Folder 9-10)
    - Treasurer, 11.0.1.
      - 11.0.1. Treasurer, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Financial Services, 11.0.2.
      - 11.0.2. Financial Services, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Forbes Reinsurance, 11.0.2.1.
      - 702.01. Forbes Reinsurance, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
      - 11.0.2.1. Forbes Reinsurance, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - 11.0.2.1. Forbes Reinsurance, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - 11.0.3. Forbes Reinsurance, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Tri-Century Insurance, 11.0.2.2.
      - 11.0.2.2. Tri-Century Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - 11.0.2.2. Tri-Century Insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.0.4. Tri-Century Insurance, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Freedom Insurance, 11.0.2.3.
      - 11.0.2.3. Freedom Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - 11.0.2.3. Freedom Insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - 11.0.5. Freedom Insurance, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Cathedral Insurance Co., 11.0.2.4.
      - 11.0.2.4. Cathedral Insurance Co., 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - 11.0.6. Cathedral Insurance Co., 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Admissions and Student Aid, 11.1.
      - 11.1. Admissions and Student Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
      - 11.1. Admissions and Student Aid, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - 11.1. Admissions and Student Aid, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 12-13)
    - PHEAA, 11.1.1.
      - 11.1.1. PHEAA, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - 11.1.1. PHEAA, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - 11.1.1. PHEAA, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Book Center, 11.2.
      - 11.2. Book Center, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - 11.2. Book Center, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Office of the Budget, 11.3.
      - 701.01. Budget and Audit, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - 11.3. Office of the Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 20-22)
      - 11.3. Office of the Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 23-25)
      - 11.3. Office of the Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
    - FY93 Budget, 11.3.1.
      - 11.3.1. FY93 Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.3.1. FY93 Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - FY94 Budget, 11.3.2.
      - 11.3.1. FY94 Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - 11.3.2. FY94 Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - 11.3.2. FY94 Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - 11.3.2. FY95 Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Capital Budget, 11.3.3.
      - 11.3.3. Capital Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 8-10)
      - 11.3.3. Capital Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - 11.3.3. Capital Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Capital Project Review Committee, 11.3.4.
      - 700.00A. Capital Project Review Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - 11.3.4. Capital Project Review Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - 11.3.4. Capital Project Review Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - 11.3.4. Capital Project Review Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 11.3.5.